Zhou Qi
left the company three years ago.
Wenjia'ao.
Sir,
how much longer until we get to Wenjia'ao?
Almost there.
About twenty more minutes.
Hello,
I'm here to do a cultural survey.
I'd like to know
about the customs and culture of Wenzhai Village.
I heard
that there were many talents in this village.
Then you can go to
the shop
at the west end of the village.
Ah.
The shop
is run by the former village chief.
You can go there
to ask.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
She has been
reviewing a large number of overseas project files,
especially from the UK.
The time
was around 2022.
What specific projects is she interested in?
It seems there's no particular project.
It seems more like
a broad screening.
Hmm.
Keep an eye on all the files
she accessed,
especially
the ones
she repeatedly viewed
or photocopied.
Yes.
Do we have any news
from our people in the UK?
Not yet.
I trust my intuition.
When the truth is revealed,
Ji Ming will feel the pain.
Only then
can he truly wake up.
Sir,
you must have lived here for many years.
Yes,
I was born and raised here,
never left.
Oh,
then you must know many old stories.
I heard from the old man at the entrance
that the Wen family
is a big family here.
And there's a daughter
who's particularly impressive.
She married into a big family in the city
and became a big boss.
Are you talking about
the daughter of Wen Laosan?
Shi Yi, right?
Yes.
Her family was the poorest
in this village.
Wen Laosan was in poor health,
and his wife
died early.
She survived with the help of a distant cousin's family,
who constantly
assisted them.
Distant cousin?
Is he also from our village?
Yes.
His name is...
Well.
His name is
Wu Zhanshan.
His family was better off at that time,
and helped
Shi Yi's family a lot.
Later,
Zhanshan's parents died.
Zhanshan went out to make a living.
Shiyi
is ambitious
and studious.
Later, she went to college.
And then,
she married a rich man
and became a rich lady.
Then,
they must have
a very good relationship.
Well,
after Shi Yi became rich,
he didn't come back much.
It's Zhanshan who came back a few times
to repair his parents' grave.
Well,
he's quite the man.
I heard
he works for Shi Yi,
driving for her.
That's good.
They can take care of each other.
Ah.
Take care of each other.
Who knows?
It's a tragedy.
A tragedy?
What does it mean?
Oh.
I can't say it.
You can't say it?
Distant cousins.
Take care of each other.
Fated lovers.
What?
She went to Wenjia Village?
Yes.
What did they do?
I didn't get too close.
She just looked around
and talked to the old village chief.
The old village chief?
What did they talk about?
I'm not sure about the details.
I didn't dare to ask
in case of causing trouble.
The old village chief?
Morning.
Morning, Mr. Lin.
What's up?
Didn't sleep well?
Oh.
I've been sorting out some historical issues.
I don't want to leave any hidden risks.
All the documents are here.
Historical issues?
Any findings?
I'm looking at some
old overseas projects.
The previous management
was quite lax.
Many fund flows
are unclear,
Especially a person named
Zhou Qi.
Zhou Qi?
I don't remember him.
I hadn't taken over yet at that time.
It was my mom in charge.
Did Director Wen
ever directly manage
the specific overseas business?
Yes, in the early days.
She's good at English,
and helped my dad a lot.
Later, when I took over,
she gradually stepped back.
Ms. Wen
is really capable.
Wen Shiyi has too many issues.
But to investigate her,
we need audit access.
Audit?
Liu Yaru.
But it takes time to win her over.
After all, her audit rights are limited.
Now,
As long as we make Bai Qiang case criminal.
it's just a matter of time
to dig out Wen Poetic through S club.
Jiang Lin,
I'm counting on you.
[My mom's health is not good.]
[She keeps talking about you.]
[Do you have time]
[to come and see her?]
[Why do you suddenly go to Mingcheng for internship?]
[The teacher arranged it.]
[They can accept me.]
[It's good.]
[Mr. Jiang.]
[Do your best.]
[Thank you, Mr. Gu.]
That's my mom.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of her for you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's okay.
You're like my mom.
My parents passed away early.
I should thank you
for giving me a chance to be a daughter.
You silly girl,
what are you talking about?
This will always
be your home.
Jiang,
the materials you provided,
especially this anonymous email
with the Zhou Man lead,
are very specific.
Yes, sir.
I've already verified
The bank accounts
and transfer records
mentioned in the email
highly match the transaction records
provided by Niu Dingshan.
Moreover,
Bai Qiang did maintain
similar romantic relationships
with at least three men
during the same period,
all pointing to Zhou Man being behind it.
This is indeed
no longer a simple civil dispute.
If the content of the email is true,
Bai Qiang's behavior
is suspected
of having the purpose of illegal possession,
fabricating facts,
concealing the truth,
and defrauding others of their property.
Moreover,
the amount is particularly huge,
which may constitute
the crime of fraud.
Yes.
And S club
may involve organizing and training personnel
to carry out such actions.
Yes.
There is even suspicion of money laundering.
This has already exceeded
the jurisdiction of our civil court.
Jiang,
you've done well.
The court
is obligated to transfer
criminal leads
to the police
during civil
proceedings.
This
not only protects
the victim's rights,
but also
to uphold judicial fairness.
Understood.
I'll prepare the transfer letter and evidence list
to hand over to the public security authorities.
Good.
Jiang,
do you know
the source of this anonymous letter?
You're very sharp this time.
But
you should protect yourself.
Especially in cases
like this,
there's often
more to it.
Ms. Liu,
what a surprise.
Please, have a seat.
Guan Tian,
let's cut to the chase.
Tell me,
you approached Lin Jiming
to take down my brother.
What do you want?
Just money and status?
I don't understand what you mean.
My job
is to solve problems for Mr. Lin.
Solve problems?
You're the one
who creates the most problems.
Every time you step in to solve a problem,
you make Lin Jiming more dependent on you,
and you become more deeply embedded in the Lin family.
In my view,
you are like
a precise scalpel.
Every cut
is made at a critical point.
What do you want to do?
Ms. Liu,
if you're here today
to question
my identity and purpose,
you've come to the wrong person.
I'm very busy.
Was that anonymous email
sent by you?
How about
we talk somewhere else?